NAA Records 5246
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
NAA Records
1960-1982
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Academy of Arbitrators (NAA)
5246
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Records of the National Academy of Arbitrators, including minutes (1964-1965), convention files (1963-1964), treasurer's records (1964), and photographs (1965-1985)
5621142
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 06, 2005
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 22, 2017
Scope and Contents
Records of the National Academy of Arbitrators, including minutes (1964-1965), convention files (1963-1964), treasurer's records (1964), and approximately 100 photographs (1965-1985).
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5775: NAA Records 5796: NAA Additional Records 5985: NAA Additional Files Regarding Proceedings 6004: NAA Additional Records 6004 AV: NAA Audio-Visual Material 6004 OHM: NAA History Committee Oral History Interview Masters 6004 OHT: NAA History Committee Oral History Interview Transcripts 6004 OHT: NAA History Committee Oral History Interview Transcripts 6004 OHT: NAA History Committee Oral History Interview Transcripts 6205: NAA Committee Files 6316: National Academy of Arbitrators Archives Project Records
Arbitration, Industrial; McKelvey, Jean T. (Jean Trepp), 1908-; Rehmus, Charles M.; National Academy of Arbitrators
5621142
- Academy - 1964-5 Bd., 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Academy - 1963 Convention (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Academy - 1964 Convention Proposal, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- NAA - Treasure's Records - 1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Academy - Treasurer's File - 1963 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- 1964 - Treasures - NAA (Box 2, Folder 2)
- NAA - Treasurers Reports - 1964 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Academy - Communications - 1963 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Misc. Pictures of NAA Members and Meetings Folder #1, 1960-1982 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  14 Photographs
- Misc. Pictures of NAA Members and Meetings Folder #2, 1960-1982 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  20 Photographs
- Misc. Pictures of NAA Members and Meetings Folder #3, 1960-1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  About 100 Photographs
- Text digitized from the collection. (Box 4)